Mona Shaban Frontend Developer

≥ mona00mona1997@gmail.com

+970599923814

▼ Portfolio

in Mona Mohammed

ABOUT ME

I'm a highly skilled Frontend Developer specializing in React.js.

My expertise lies in building reusable and flexible components and integrating APIs.

I am always passionate about learning and undertaking new challenges, constantly evolving, and enjoying dealing with problems and providing optimal solutions

I look forward to an opportunity where I can exploit my skills and further develop them, I have the capability and confidence to work independently or within a team.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer (React.js), Al-Qeeq Company

02/2023 - 09/2023 | Gaza, Palestine

full-time

- Responsible for developing interfaces for websites and dashboards.
- API integration using redux-saga.

Frontend Developer

03/2023 - 03/2023 | Saudi Arabia

Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

Frontend Developer

02/2023 - 02/2023 | Gaza, Palestine

Lawyers Dashboard

- Convert PSD using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

Frontend Developer

02/2023 - 02/2023 | Turkey

Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

React.js Developer, Ajyal Incubator

10/2022 - 12/2022 | Gaza

Landing Page and Dashboard

- Responsible for building the UI using components.
- Using styled-components, bootstrap, reactstrap, ckeditor5-react.
- API integration using redux-thunk, and redux-saga.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.
- Working within a team.

Frontend Developer, FoxyTech Company

09/2022 – present | Istanbul, Turkey

part-time

• Responsible for developing interfaces for websites.

Frontend Trainer, Safi Design

06/2022 - 09/2022 | Khanyounes, Palestine

Frontend Development (70 hrs)

- HTML/ HTML5
- CSS/ CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- GitHub

Frontend Developer, Mohtawa company

2022 | Kuwait

Website

An introductory website for a Saudi company working in the field of e-marketing and managing social media platforms.

- Developed the interfaces using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.
- Add animation to a website.

Frontend Developer, Highnox

2021 – 2021 | Sweden

Dashboard

Dashboard for the accountants' program.

- Convert UI/UX design to a perfect pixel dashboard.
- Using HTML, pure CSS.
- Use charts and the Drag and Drop technique.

Frontend Developer, Krogarna.se

2021 | Sweden

Dashboard

A dashboard is special for selling courses so that free courses or for a fee are uploaded, and a certificate is given at the end of the course.

The interfaces of three sections of this dashboard have been developed, one for admin, one for employees, and one for students.

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

Frontend Developer, Al-sharq Feloowship Program

2021 | Palestine

Educational Website

- Convert Figma design using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.

React.js Developer, GGateway

2021 | Palestine

ProShop Store

- Responsible for building the UI.
- API integration using React-redux.
- Using redux-thunk as a middleware.
- Responsible for the high performance of the website.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.

EDUCATION

BA, Al Quds Open University

08/2015 - 12/2020 | Rafah, Palestine

Computer Information System



- React.js
- React-redux
- Redux-toolkit
- HTML/5

• CSS/3

- JavaScript
- jQuery

Bootstrap

GitHub

Sass

- · Responsive design
- API integration

- Styled-component
- Redux-thunk
- React-router
- · React-hooks

React-Bootstrap



Arabic English